<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>redns-docs</title>
    <link>https://mfaltys.github.io/redns_docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content on redns-docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Released under the MIT license</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mfaltys.github.io/redns_docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Milestone 1</title>
      <link>https://mfaltys.github.io/redns_docs/milestone.1/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mfaltys.github.io/redns_docs/milestone.1/index/</guid>
      <description>Executive Summary Many industry malware detection tools (used in the workplace or for personal use) are either platform specific, intrusive, or high overhead and need to be maintained. Redns is a malware detection tool which plans to overcome these problems in a small, easy to deploy package.
Goals and Objectives Redns plans to combat the problems outined in the executive summary in the following ways:
 Easy to impliment If its run as the main DNS server it can detect malicious content without having to run any client-side software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Milestone 2</title>
      <link>https://mfaltys.github.io/redns_docs/milestone.2/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mfaltys.github.io/redns_docs/milestone.2/index/</guid>
      <description>Architectural Diagram Components The following components are used in this tool:
 DOIC: The main tool itself, comprised of components to parse the DNS request recieved, check the requested domain against the malicious domain list (in redis), and resolving the request upstream if it is deemed safe.
Listens on TCP:53. Redis DB: The redis db (listens on TCP:6379) containing the following data sets:
 blacklist:domain: contains a redis set of blacklisted domains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Redns Configuration</title>
      <link>https://mfaltys.github.io/redns_docs/configuration/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:11:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mfaltys.github.io/redns_docs/configuration/index/</guid>
      <description>Configuration TODO</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DNS based IOC</title>
      <link>https://mfaltys.github.io/redns_docs/index/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 21:07:13 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mfaltys.github.io/redns_docs/index/</guid>
      <description>Redns is a DNS based indicator of compromise (IOC) written in go. This tool is designed to be a very low overhead plug-and-play approach to implimenting an IOC for organizational or personal use. If you want to track our day-to-day activities, check out our trello board.
Using redns Getting precompiled binaries This project pushes up a binary on every project commit and tag. You can find these binaries in the following locations (note we only pre compile for 64 bit linux architectures):</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>